http://www.coopportunity.com/privacy

Co+op Deals
Everyone Saves!
Read how we're responding to the COVID-19 situation
Cart$0.000Your cart is empty.
Co+op Deals
Everyone Saves!
Privacy Policy
Co-opportunity is committed to protecting your privacy online. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on the coopportunity.com website.
The Information We Collect
Our site’s online forms may require users to give us personal information such as their name, address, email, zip code, etc.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Chrome), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Time Warner, Comcast).
How We Use the Information
Co-opportunity does not sell, trade or give away data or information we receive about you from our website. This applies to personal information, email addresses, and any other information that may be provided by you to access and use our website.
We use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products and services, and to respond to your inquiries about our offerings.
We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products or services.
We will disclose information we maintain when we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law. For example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request.
Agents and contractors of Co-opportunity who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Co-opportunity.
Collection of Information by Others
Our site contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by these third parties.
Cookies
Like most major sites, Co-opportunity places “cookies” on a user’s computer, which enables us to determine the user’s operating system, browser type and version, ISP, top-level domain, and other such general information.
Cookies are used for several purposes. Cookies enable our site to load faster in a user’s browser on subsequent visits. Information from cookies allow us to track traffic flow to and from our site, which assists us in marketing, web promotions and helps us create a site that will best serve the needs of our users.
Cookies are a standard industry technology and do not contain any personally identifying information such as your email address. Nor can cookies contain a virus. In addition, the information in cookies placed on your computer from Co-opportunity’s website are not accessible by other websites. Co-opportunity’s site doesn’t use or allow third-party cookies.
Users have the ability to configure their browsers to refuse acceptance of cookies, which are little pieces of information (alphanumeric identifiers), which sites transfer to a user’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes during each visit. The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to manage the cookies on your computer.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy policy for this site, you may contact us at service@coopportunity.com.
Privacy Policy Changes
Our privacy policy may change at any time. If our information practices changes in any significant way, we will post the policy changes here. This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 16, 2016.
